Name:Doraemon
(Peipei Medicine)
What? Nobita ? Stomach ache ?
The you can't have this bread
What do you want? Doraemon?
I'm not having a stomach ache
The bread is delicious
But it's eaten, it's gone
Don't eat it, it'd be
there but you don't know the taste
Wonder if we can eat it and
it won't become less
What? Troubled by this ?
Are you going to take some
tool out?
Peipei medicine It increases
amount to anything
Just a drop on the top ?
Forget it,
this may be dangerous
Why dangerous ?
Don't be stingy, come on
Will you promise me one thing ?
Whatever increased on the bread
don't eat it
Ok, ok
Nothing happens
Not yet
It increases every 5 minutes
The first 5 minutes
one will become two
I know it, the next 5 minutes
two will become four
Just like that
Four will become eight
Eight will become ...many
It's about 5 minutes now
It increased
How wonderful
Let's each have one
Wait, if we ate it,
there'll be nothing left
Wait another 5 minutes
they'll become four
Then I don't want them
Red bean cake is better
Look
It becomes four
Got it. If we have one left
each time
Then we can never finish it
I wonder if we pass the 5 minute
faster
Then, I'm going to eat now
Delicious
This tasted so good
No, I had enough
Mom
Thank you so much for taking care of me
Please have some bread
Want to ask mom to have some?
Come, eat as you like
That's wonderful
No
No, Can't have left-overs,
must finish them
No, I can't have no more
Oh, no
the leftover will increases
It increases again
Doraemon, help me
Find some one to eat them all
It increases again
Nobita, what should I do?
Shizuka, please helo
Eat bread ?
Invite me to eat? Ok I'll go
It has increased so many
Nobita
Just in time
Why so panicking ?
Never mind, hurry
These are all for us ?
How wonderful
I'm going to eat now
I love Lesi bread
This is delicious, super delicious
Really great
Come, have as much as you like
I can't do it no more. Can have
any more
No, you have to finish it all
Delicious
I'm fulled now
Can't eat no more
No, Jian, finish them all
Dorn, you're so noisy
I'll sacrefy myself and eat it all
No
Mom, help me
help me to eat the last one
You're too much, Nobita
It increases again
Doraemon, I understand now
please help me
What should I do? What should I do?
Throw them away
Throw it here
the Garbage truck will take them
The rest is not no of my business
Are you reading ?
Yes Did you eat all the
bread without any leftover
There shouldn’t be anything left
Otherwise it will be horrible
I...did eat them all
ls it? That is good
What do you mean horrible?
If you have one left
In 5 minutes the amount will
increase
You know how many of them
it will be in one hour
About a hundred ?
No, it's 4096 of them
In 2 hours, it'll be
167billion of them
Wow, wow..
Then in 15 minutes,
it'll become trillion
In one day the earth will be
covered
There are some left
What did you say?
Oh, no. This is serious
What can you do thins
I can't help it
but find a place to trush it
Trush it? Where?
The universe is huge
Use the rocket to sent these
to far far away
Ok
All set
Good, set the fire
That is the Lesi Bread Galaxy
Real Lesi Bread ?
Yes. Did you eat all the bread
without any left over
You just look up to the sky
You'll see it for sure
(Mixed up O'clock)
Nobita, you're playing, not
studying, and didn't clean up
Mom has mom's work
I can't always do yours
Are you listening or not?
When mom and dad were kids
we all had to help out at home
Not just that, study hard too
Comparing with you
Mom's lips are exercising
Up till now
repeating the same things again & again
Don't how many time before she
is satisfied
Time like this is always no ending
I think it's about time to end
But, according to mom, it's hard
to say
Can't help it, Mom is mom
Stop
I need to go
How terrible. Really
Doraemon, how long has it
been
15 minutes
That means still 45 minutes coming
Mom's lecture usually will take
about one hour
Terrible, Shizuka is coming soon
You'd better think of something
Doraemon
Since you have an oppointment
I'll think of something
Use this
Mixed up O'clock
Try it
First put the rewind to c
Then put the counter to 60
And push the night button
That way, the time will past
In a 60 times speed
I did not feel anything
No, the passing of time is faster
We just stay
outside of the time
ls it?
Look at the clock
Turning in a high speed
Even watching TV too...Look
Really, Just like the cartoon
everyone moves very fast
See, I told you it's true
It's real
Doraemon, it's getting dark
It's about evening
Are you kidding
Shizuka is coming
Don't worry
only the time in the room pass faster
Step outside
you see, the sun is still up
Have to put the button to normal
How long do you want me to wait
Yes, right away
Ok, please continue
It's about 20 times faster
Just like the fast forward tape
recorder
I wonder what mom is talking
about
Weird, feel so tired than usual
Cool, ok, give me back the
Mixed up O'clock
Let me borrow it again
It seems so interesting
This is not for playing
Wait give it back to me
Give it back to me
Only in this room, the time moves
100 time slower
You stay out
It'll take about 2-3 hours
The bye
Wait, Nobita, I'm not finish yet
Doraemon, what are you
doing
Nobita...
Shizuka is so slow, I go pick her up
Be careful
you're so slow
Dorn
I want to put your time slower
You're the one make the
mistake
Drive so fast in this ally
I'll teach you a lesson
Really, Can't understand what
people thing lately
You can go now
Shizuka
Sorry, I'm late
Never mind, never mind
I can think about the time matter
If people can control time freely
it would be nice
Ya, that's true
Let me bring you some tea,
please wait
Thank you so much
Mom, mom
Mom?
Not in
Went out shopping?
It's empty
Forget it, never mind
20 times is good
In one bleank the water is boiled
What should we play?
What to play?
Lot of time
If you want
No matter how many days,
how many months are fine with me
How about Pocket cards
I can only play guessing cards
How about the rest?
No
How about listen to music then?
I only have Doraemon album
I got tired of it long time ago
I hate wasting time, do you
know it?
Hey, don't be so angry
Please be relax, ok?
As long as the two of us together
we'll be happy, right?
As long as I can look at you
like this I'll be very happy
A kind of peace
Just like in the dream
Nobita
Did I fall into asleep
I'm sorry
Got to recover the time
Nobita, you are taking a nap
I'm going home
Shizuka , do you have to go ?
You just got here
Too bad
Oh, no
I forgot to recover the time in
the room
Shizuka
What? Oh,no
It's dark out
Nobita, what is going on ?
That's why I told you this is not
playing
I'm sorry
(Avalanche at the study room)
Wow, cool
Well, not bad, right? This is
new
My ski board is great too
It's Doghlas Farpo
Mind is brand name too
What kind of ski board do you
use?
I don't have one
You can ask your parents to buy
one
I know, I know
You can't ski, that's why we
don't buy it
Right
You nonsense, I say we will buy
it, I'll ask my parents to buy it
Hopefully, daddy won't buy
ski board for me
What? You want to go ski?
That is great
But, daddy, ski board is so
expensive. You won't buy it
Wait
You see, I knew sooner or later
So, I's prepared
Here, take it
Cool
Nobita, you hate skiing
I'm worried about it
You mentioned it to your father
Makes him very happy
Nobita, this is great
Wonderful
Luckily...no, not it
Unfortunately, there no snow
Can't go skiing now
Honey, the weather report says
there'll be snow tonight
Cool, we can go skiing then
Doraemon
Doraemon, please thing of
something to help me
Everyone wanted me to go skiing
Wanting to see me fall
Just practice for a while. You'll
be all right
No snow now, how can I practice
Then, wait until it snows
Wait until then, will be too late
Oh, can't do anything at all
Are you going to take
something out
What is this
Indoor skiing machine
Just climb on it
and start skiing
The belt will move according
to the speed
Then you can skiing for along
time
Change a direction
the board will change direction too
If you stop
the belt will stop
How interesting
let me borrow it
First of all, put on your ski board
Get up there, and work hard
Stand on the top and skiing
Wow, wow
When you fall, you fall
What? You want to stop now?
If you don't practice, it'll hurt
Come practice
No, I don't want to practice here
Must have a back ground white
snow
Then I'll be in the mood
I'll give you the back ground then
Ah?
Ya, Ah
What is going on?
I'm playing 3D movie
Ok, start practice
Belt is about there
When skiing, the back ground
will move too
When fall, there's
smoke of snow too
The snow is not cold
no mood, I don't want to practice
Being picky again
You mean the snow should be
icy
If you're in the mood
you'll practice?
Yes
Then I can't help it
At first, I did not want to use
this button
So cold, so cold
How about that ? In the mood now
Don't run away
It hurts
It's so cold here, I'm taking a muffler
I'll take it for you
Ok, put it on and skiing
Please, I think even if I'm not
good at it, that's fine
This is your weakness
If it didn't turn out all right,
you give up right away
This way, you can't do anything right
You're making me so worried
Sorry, I should not hate you
As long as you understands
Good, I'll try very hard to fall
I mean practice
Just around here
Ok, going skiing now
Good, you're getting better
So, skiing is so much fun
You are moving around,won't
feel cold
I'm so afraid of the cold
No, I better adjust the temperature
It should be this button
Worn, so cold
Too much
It's too cold to skiing
I don't want to play now,
I'll be frozen to death
Where is the exist
Exist, exist
Ah?
Hurry, think of something
What should we do ?
It should not be on the machine
How weird
Doraemon, Doraemon
Oh, no. Doraemon is buried
in the snow
I've to save him
Weird
Didn't see the exist for so long
This should be my study room
Who come to save me please
Someone, anyone,
please come help me
Help
So noisy, what is he doing?
Help, someone please help
Ah, what are you doing?
Help, please help
Ah, help me
(Sesame lock)
Why hide here
You're afraid of losing face
you don't want to be find out
But if you didn't tell mom
she'll loss face big time
Really
why do I have a son like you
I wonder if you are just like
your dad
You're way over the bottom line
What are you doing at school
anyway?
Why didn't you study hard?
If you want to, you can make it
Use the passion of playing games
To your study
Don't ever try to hide it up
from mom
What?
Mom is too much she opens
my drawer without letting me know first
She found my test
This is terrible
You should be scolded
Right?
Please put a lock on my drawer
Good idea
You shouldn’t do that anyway
Not only the zero ones, but
the tests too
Hiding the test is not right?
ls it?
It is
Did you say I should not hind
the test
What are you trying to do
My red bean cake
Don't take away, that is mine
You say I should not hide the test
ok, I'll give the tool
Sesame Lock
Sesame Close the door
Try Open it
Can't open it at all
Sesame Open
Sesame Close
Cool, can I do it too?
Sesame Open, Sesame Open
Open Sesame, Sesame Open
The door will remember
the voice of the person using the key
And not listening to others
ok, you try
Sesame Close
Like that
No problem
I want to try it
This is a secret
If mom found out, it would be terrible
Hide this in the drawer
These two are so bad
What did he hide this time?
Heysu
It's so hard to open
Experiment accomplished
You tease your mom
Dorn
Nobita, don't run, stop
Sesame close
Hey, open the door Nobita
Hey, open the door
The key is so great
Ok, let me help friends in trouble
Shizuka
I want to tell you
a safe way to keep secrets
What is that ?
Are you serious ?
This is the key to keep your
secret
Only 10 Yen each time
ls it reliable?
Is it? Then, let's try it out
Sesame Close
Can you keep a secret this way
Really
Dorn, you teased me
Don't run
Sesame Open
Dorn, stop, don't run
Sesame Close the door
Use this board to hide
Can't be open
Why not?
That stuff
just push it, it'll move
Nobita, come out of here
Can't open at all
Sesame Open
Dorn
Sesame Close
It hurts, hurts so much
Sesame open
What?
What a powerful key
This should be safe
I need it for my room
I won't let anyone to open
my diary
Then.. I would like to lock my
piggy bank
Give it back to me after you
finish
Ok, bye
I'll be waiting here
hurry
Makes 30 Yen
So slow, are they forgetting?
It's raining
It's raining, go hide
They forgot ?
It's so fun, and perhaps too
much
Nobita
Ah? Did he go home ?
I'm here
Did you catch cold?
Sorry
I'm late
Here, give it back to you
Really, I've been waiting and
catch cold
I'm sorry
Sesame Open
Doraemon, it can't be open
Coming, who is it?
Doraemon, It's me, please
open the door
What? It's Nobita
I can't open it
Please help
Only the person with key can
open it
Say that again
Sesame Open
Oh
your cold affects your voice
Before you recover
it won't be open
Sesame Open
The voice is still not working
Terrible
(Sticky Coin)
So much trouble
It is trouble
Wonder if can be tolerated
What should I do?
How terrible
Nobita is something bothering you?
I can't stand it no more
Doraemon, any
machine can go places without walking
I guess so
This is the sticky coin
Sticky coin?
Yes, there's kind
of fish called sticky coin
The one with a coin on
it's forehead?
It will stick on the big fish
And go around everywhere
with the big fish
The coin is like that
If you wear it on the back
You can sick on anyone you
wish
Let the person
take you anywhere
Here put it on
Just like this?
Yes it can stick on anyone
No, don't stick on me,
don't come near
I'm going to stick now
No, no
It's true
Use that, you'll become a lazy
worm
Just for today
We had Marathon today at school
I'm so tire now
Really
Thank you
Here is fine?
I just want to go to the toilet
You're so lazy
Great
with this tool, everything is so easy
Who should I stick to this time
to outside?
Great so easy
No, no, don't go that way
I don't want to go that way
Who is that?
Weird
Can't help it, wait for someone
else to pass by
Kind of tickling
Perhaps I think too much
Great
Doraemon, look
Where is he?
Give me back the coin
Stop, don't do that
It hurts
Monsters, you touch girl's behind
Low class
Bye now
Stop, or you'll be sorry
I'm going to leave you alone
Anyway, it's me
No, it's me
It's me
Me
I say it's me
Me...
No, it's me
What's wrong with you all ?
We are talking about who run
the fastest
What? I thought you're fighting
And then? Who is the fastest?
Of course it's me
If you don't believe it, let's run
Make a circle along the street
and back here
Really
Start
Heysu
I'm going first
So, I'm the fastest person
You cheated
We didn't see Nobita running
That's because I'm so fast that
you can't see me
You cheated
Yes
Cheating
Cheating cheating cheating
What?
You say I was cheating?
Cheating cheating cheating
Who's cheating?
What?
Weird
I did see Nobita running
It's too easy
Jian, jian
Jian is a big music idiot
What did you say?
What?
Saying bad thing about others,
better be careful
I forgive you today
Really
So much fun
How do I stop this?
No one is here
it's so quiet too, I can practice here
Lalala
Feel so terrible
Passing the old oak tree
the place I miss you
Super horrible voice
Spring of the north
Season in the city
Worn fart
Wonder where is Nobita
Doraemon
What happen to you?
Give you back this
I got scared
So I say
don't play too much
(Machine ball)
What's going on with this?
Why is your room so messy?
Clean it up at once and
clean the room too
You need to pull out the weed
today
Before mom comes back
you better finish them all
Really
Mom is in a bad mood today
Next...
where did I start just now
I'm back
Just in time
Don't seem to be a good time
to come home
I'm leaving
Wait
Help me, Doraemon
Cleaning UP?
This is good for you
Better clean up then
Impossible for me to finish
help
Clean up your own messy world
That's good
Please don't say that. Please
I beg you
Whenever you ask
I take out the tool from my pocket
This
Machine ball
Everyone of it
has a computer motor
Put it on
Everyone can be a machine man
Go back to your position
Thank you
That will de
Mai
Stand up
Everyone go home
Become so neat
This is great, so easy
Hey, come over here
This time come over here
Clean all the conor
This time clean the floor
Hey, start
Then pull the weed, start
That is it
I don't have to do anything
So easy
Right, some music
Hey, change something fun
Thirsty, some juice
It's really noisy Stop
The broken thing
Maybe it's too old
Right, buy a new one
I'm going to check everyone's
work
Feel like a king
so much fun
Got the water everywhere in the
hall way, what are you doing
Stop
If not working hard
I throw you into the garbage yard
Be serious
broken vacuum
Understand ? Dorn
Understand, then work hard
Do it yourself if you can
Ya, ya, ya
Ohoo
Look down upon machine man
Beat the human up
Oh,no
Help. Help. Help
It's so terrible
So cold
I understand now, I'm sorry
Everyone, I apology
Help
So terrible, terrible
Take back the machine ball
with magnet
Who tell you to order people
around like that
Doraemon
This time you clean up yourself
This is a good lesson
Worse that just now
I'm home
Mom's home
You are not cleaning up yet
What are you doing
so slow, hurry
Or mom is not going to forgive
you, be careful I'll tell daddy
Understand ? Nobita
I understand
(Weird umbrella)
You are clean up
It rains the red rain
In your case, it's red snow
Candy
Is it candy?
That one is mine
Must be the one I forgot to eat
Founder the keeper
Can't help it
If you can see through my
magic, the candy is yours
Use magic to decide?
If you can't , then the candy is
mine
Look, there's candy here
Put it behind you
Good, here
This time, put it behind you again
Take it from the back to the
front
Then, throw it to the yard
There's nothing here
Weird, it was here...
Get up, and see
Good, let me show you
No
Ah, it' s candy(sound the same
as rain)
How can it be?
Where? Where is candy?
I mean rain. The weather changed
How terrible, it rains all of a
sudden
Yes, honey is coming back soon
Better get him a umbrella
Nobita take this to train station
Hurry, daddy must be waiting
Shizuka
You don't have umbrella
Nobita
It suddenly rains
I can't go home now
Then use mine
Come please
But, aren't you going to pick
up your daddy
Never mind. We can use it together
ls it? Then I'll borrow your
umbrella, thank you
Any time, bye
Good, hurry
Nobita, Nobita
Let me borrow it too
Not this one
What do you mean
Shizuka can, why can't I
No, not like that
Then let me borrow it
No
Without umbrella, how can I
pick up daddy
HEY
Honey
Not here yet
He went out very early
You wait just for a while
Nobita is not at the station yet?
His daddy is waiting for him
Wonder where is this child?
Let me go see
Be careful
Did you have umbrella with you?
I have an umbrella with me
Searching umbrella
Where is Nobita now?
Just follow the arrow
Heysu, heysu
This way
Found him
What's wrong with you ?
Doraemon
He bully me
Jian
He took away my umbrella?
Just can't help these kids
So slow, what are they doing?
Daddy, sorry we are late
So late
I began to worry
Where is my umbrella?
There are many of them
Here
This one has many flower on it
$0 pretty
This thing can not be used
Then don't use it
Look like child's thing
Never mind. As long as we can
go home
Ah, Ya
This is a music umbrella
It makes us the focus
Please take out something without
any decoration
I think this one is good
No decoration on this one
So heavy
That's for training arm muscle
Nothing lighter than this?
Yes, a good one
Bat umbrella
Ah?
So light. Can't even walk
Let me down, help
Daddy doesn't look very happy
Let him down please
Where did daddy fly to ?
Ah, he is here
Hey, I'm here, come help me
Where is bat?
It flow away
Use the umbrella from high to
the ground
I thought we were finished
Why use this one this time
Rain has stopped, we don't need
it
Since I have taken it here
please use it
That will make us look so dumb
I'll hold it
Just use it will be fine
When you see mom
just say luckily we brought you umbrella
Ah?
Oh, no
What kind of umbrella is this?
You always have some weird thing
Stop Doraemon
(If Phone Booth)
Great, flying fly
If wind blows, it can fly even
higher
Getting higher and higher
Nobita's kite, which one is it?
That one? That one?This one?
Dorn, the lazy kite
Are you all right?
What are you doing ?
Forget it
hate this childish game
Do you want to play shuttlecock
I like to play with girls
Let's go
Go, let's go
One, two, three
If loss, don't put on the ink
No, you must
Come here
Why everyone playing the
boring game in new year
Welcome home
I've prepare bandage and hot water
How did you now
Of course
every year the same
It's so tiring having new year
I want to go somewhere without
kite and shuttlecock
Really want to go?
If phone booth
This is an experiment
Let if and theory become real
tool
Hey, please give us the world
with no kite and shuttlecock
Then soon there'll be answer
That is it
Feeling nothing changed
Look at the sky
No kites
How boring
During new year
no kids' entertainment
Everyone looks so bored
Why didn't you play kite
and shuttlecock
How?
How to play this? It's impossible
You really don't know
Never seen it, never heard of it
Doraemon
take out kite and shuttlecock
Why do you want that in this world
No one here has ever play kite
and shuttlecock
I wish to be like this since I
was very young
I can be a leader here
This is kite
Looks kind of fun
We want one too
Doraemon, take it out for
everyone
Then...
I heard that Nobita invent this
How unique
See, everyone respect me
It's easy to play
Watch very carefully
Run run run...
So, just pull and run like this
Just like that
Look who's the best
Pulling kite competition
First play it and have so much fun
Looks very interesting
but stir up dirt
Nobita
Are you going home ?
Actually, I hate that simple game
You loss and don't admit it
Oh, ya, Doraemon
take out the shuttlecock
Look
use the rocket hit the cock
The one losses, the face will be painted
Do you want to try
Nobita, what is that? New game?
Teach us
It's popular
I can do it too
Kind of nervous
Relax
Do as I tell, and will be fine
Heyo
Good
Ah?
Who won just now?
Can't hit it back
Run away fast
Let the cock fall on the ground
So difficult
My turn
ok?
Coming now
hey
HEY
Hey...ah..
I want to run but just catch it
accidentally
We can't win Nobita
Of course, no one can
do very well at the beginning
Nobita
The kite flow into the sky by itself
We couldn't hold it
I'm so useless
Teach us how to do it like you
do
I don't care, leave me alone
I'm not responsible for this
Never
No of my business
Don't laugh Doraemon
I tell you not to laugh